galahotels.com 2007-12-04

# Untitled Page

**

## PRIVACY& POLICY

**We use order forms that allow you to book a hotel room. We collect your name, e-mail address, postal address, and credit card information. This information is used to process and check orders. We also use this information to contact you in case there is a question or problem with a reservation.

We also use data collected when you register, enter a contest, and make purchases to enhance and personalize your booking experience. We strongly value your privacy. Your personal information provided to our web will NOT be passed along for secondary use without your explicit permission.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer this website. We log IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to track a user"s specific session, or to investigate cases of fraud or other security violations on our site. Any personally identifiable information contained in our IP address logs will be treated with the same respect for your privacy that order and registration information is treated.

**What are cookies and should I worry about them ?**

Cookies are small pieces of information that many web sites use to make online navigation easier. This data is contained on your hard drive in a file which your web browser provides for the purpose. A cookie can contain information such as a user ID. Our site can"t read other data on your hard drive or read cookies created by other sites.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your travel cart. You do not need to have cookies turned on to view our site, but you will need to accept cookies to fill the online reservation form.

**Links ?**

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites - this privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

**Who else has access to the information I provide to Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com ?**

Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com does not sell, rent, or give away your personal information to anyone. We may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with applicable law or with legal process served on Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com, or the public.

**What about my credit card number ?**

When it comes to fill the online reservation form, you might be worried about your credit card. All transaction related information will be passed on to the trusted financial institution, and we do NOT maintain in our server all or part of your financial information, including but not limited to credit card"s name, number and expiry date.

**What is Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com doing to protect my privacy ?**

This site has security measures in place to protect from the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. Our servers use encrypted methods for those pages which contain personally identifiable data, including your credit card and address. We routinely and zealously monitor and upgrade our security systems to ensure that we use the best security technology available.

**Changes to our Privacy Statement**

Any material changes in the way we use personal information will be described in future versions of this privacy statement. By booking with us you agree that our privacy statement, current at the time of your most recent booking, shall apply to all your information, whether given to us at the time of that booking or at the time of earlier bookings. If at any time we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in the privacy statement applicable to your information, we will notify you by way of an email and request your approval.

We at Internet-Hotel-Reservation.com are sincerely committed to a safe and secure web experience for our visitors. If, after reading all this, you have concerns or questions, by all means, get in touch with us.
